你觉得怎么样?
So what'd you think?
还不错
It was good.
就这样?
That's it?
"还不错"?
"Good"?
我挺喜欢的 当你告诉我
I enjoyed it. When you told me
我马上就要"失去第一次"的时候
I was going to be "losing my virginity,"
我可没想到你是指要第一次给我看
I didn't think you meant showing me Raiders of the Lost Ark
"夺宝奇兵"
for the first time.
抱歉 是我表达不清
My apologies. I chose my words poorly.
我应该说你的世界
I should have said you were about
将在我的沙发上颠倒
to have your world rocked on my couch.
谢谢你陪我看
Anyway, thank you for watching it.
这是我一直以来很喜欢的电影之一
It's one of my all-time favorites.
电影很有趣...
It was very entertaining...
虽然有很明显的故事漏洞
despite the glaring story problem.
故事漏洞?!
Story problem?!
你... Amy...
You... oh, Amy...
你这眼神不济的小笨蛋
what a dewy-eyed moon-calf you are.
"夺宝奇兵"
Raiders of the Lost Ark
是史蒂芬·斯皮尔伯格和乔治·卢卡斯的佳作
is the love child of Steven Spielberg and George Lucas,
这两位是当代最有才华的电影制作人
two of the most gifted filmmakers of our generation.
我看了36遍
I've watched it 36 times,
除了那场有蛇的还有脸融化的戏
except for the snake scene and the face-melting scene,
我只有在影院里才敢看 但是...
which I can only watch when it's still light out, but...
我不信你能找出故事漏洞
I defy you to find a story problem.
说说看... 看能不能惊得我合不拢嘴
Here's my jaw... drop it.
好吧
All right.
印第安纳·琼斯对故事发展
Indiana Jones plays no role
没有任何作用
in the outcome of the story.
哪怕电影里没有他
If he weren't in the film,
结果都是一模一样的
it would turn out exactly the same.
我知道你为什么这么说 你没看懂
Oh, I see your confusion. You don't understand.
印第安纳·琼斯是这个戴着帽子拿着鞭子的
Indiana Jones was the one in the hat with the whip.
我看懂了 如果电影里没有他
No, I do, and if he weren't in the movie,
纳粹还是会找到约柜
the Nazis would have still found the ark,
把它带上小岛 打开 然后全部死光...
taken it to the island, opened it up and all died...
结果完全一样
just like they did.
我来帮你合起来
Let me close that for ya.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第七季第四集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：影子打酱油 波特妹子 初见 捞盐不许再通宵
校对：UU在健身
嘿!
Hey!
嗨! 我以为你每周三
Hi! I thought you went
才会去漫画书店呢
to the comic book store on Wednesdays.
没错 不过Sheldon和Amy在约会
Yeah, but Sheldon and Amy were having date night
我可不想在那儿尴尬着
and they don't need me there to make it awkward.
他们俩已经够尴尬了
They have each other for that.
学校生活怎么样?
So, how was school?
很好 看看这个
Oh, good. Check it out.
"令人失望的孩子" Beverly Hofstadter著
The Disappointing Child by Beverly Hofstadter.
你买了我妈写的书?
You bought my mom's book?
没错!
Yeah!
心理学课程的推荐书单上
It's on the recommended reading list
就有这本书
for my psychology class.
拜托 别读那本书
Come on. Not that book.
里面... 写了我童年时代
It... it's got, like, every horrible story
所有的糗事
from my childhood in it.
真棒 那有照片吗?
Oh, cool. Are there pictures?
说真的 你还是换本书看吧
Seriously, please find another book.
得了吧 为什么? 有那么糟吗?
Oh, come on. Why? How bad could it be?
里面... 写了教我学用尿盆的事
There... there's chapters about potty training,
还有我尿床的事...
and bed-wetting and...
和自慰的事
masturbation.
基本上 只要有东西从我身体里出来
Basically, if something came out of me,
她就写了进去!
she wrote about it!
这样吧 你想看就看
You know what? Do whatever you want,
但千万别跟我说里面的事情
just don't talk to me about it.
哺乳危机的那章都不行?
Not even the chapter on the breast-feeding crisis?
那根本不算是危机
It was not a crisis.
我更喜欢左边的
Apparently, I favored the left one,
所以她的胸左右不对称了
she got a little lopsided.
天啊 你一直喜欢左边!
Oh, my God, you still go left!
你觉得我最像哪个名人?
Which celebrity would you say I look like the most?
哈里·贝瑞
Halle Berry.
干嘛问这个?
Why?
我和Stuart在交友网上填写个人档案
Stuart and I are putting dating profiles online,
里面就有这个问题
and it's one of the questions.
谢谢夸奖... 这个妹子的脸部轮廓我超级羡慕
And thank you... I'd kill for that woman's bone structure.
你怎么在读"傲慢与偏见"?
Why are you reading Pride and Prejudice?
我来告诉你原因
I'll tell you why.
Amy毁了我对"夺宝奇兵"的爱
Amy ruined Raiders of the Lost Ark for me,
所以现在我也得看看
so now I'm trying to find
怎么能毁了她对这本书的爱
something beloved to her and ruin that.
她还不够惨?
Because her life wasn't enough?
等等... 怎么有人能毁了"夺宝奇兵"?
Wait... how can, how can anyone ruin Raiders?
这电影很完美
It's perfect.
没错 但印第安纳·琼斯
Yeah, except for the fact
跟整个故事没有任何联系
that Indiana Jones is completely irrelevant to the story.
无论有没有他 纳粹都会找到约柜 打开 然后死掉
With or without him, the Nazis find the ark, open it and die.
嘿 等等
Hey, wait a minute.
不是这样 纳粹本来挖错了地方
No, the Nazis were digging in the wrong place.
就因为印第安纳先找到了约柜
The only reason they got the ark
他们才能找到的
was because Indy found it first.
事实上 就因为吊坠在印第安纳手里
Actually, they were only digging in the wrong place
他们才会挖错地方的
because Indy had the medallion.
要是没有他 吊坠一开始就在纳粹手里
Without him, they would have had the medallion
他们也就能挖对地方了
and dug in the right place.
好吧 我知道你不想
Okay, I know you don't
谈这件事
want to talk about it,
但我能不能就问一个书里的问题?
but can I just ask you one question about your mom's book?
不能
No.
我只是想知道
I just want to know
一个五岁男孩干嘛要涂妈妈的化妆品
why a five-year-old boy puts on his mom's makeup
还拿气球当假胸
and wears balloon boobies.
那不是假胸 是假肌肉
They weren't boobies, they were muscles.
而且我涂了绿色的彩妆
And the makeup was green.
就是想假装绿巨人
I was pretending to be The Hulk.
但你戴了她的胸罩
You were wearing her bra.
那是为了不让我的肌肉下垂!
That was to keep my muscles from sagging!
我们能不能不说这事儿了?!
Can we please stop talking about this?!
好吧 不说了
Okay, okay.
不过 作为一名
But you know, as a student of psychology
首次作业就得了优加的心理学学生...
who got a check-plus on her first homework assignment...
我认为 有时候把事情谈开了比较好
I think, sometimes, it's good to open up about these things.
好吧
Okay, fine.
你想知道我为什么打扮成绿巨人吗?
Do you want to know why I dressed like The Hulk?
因为我总是生我妈的气
Because I was always mad at my mom
想从那个家砸出一条生路来
and I wanted to smash my way out of that house.
你为什么那么生气?
Well, why were you so angry?
天 我不知道 或许是因为
Gee, I don't know. Maybe it's because
我总是她那些小实验的对象
I was always the subject of her little experiments.
你看到那章没 她导演了一场没有彩蛋的复活节寻蛋活动
Did you get to the chapter where she staged the Easter egg hunt
就想看我会找多久
with no eggs to see how long I'd keep looking?
我一直找到了六月(复活节在三月)
The answer, by the way: June.
小傻瓜 很抱歉 我真希望
Sweetie, I'm so sorry. I wish there was something
我可以做些什么让你好受点
I could do to make you feel better.
我也希望 但没有
I do, too, but there's not.
真的吗? 你确定?
Really? Are you sure about that?
也是 优加的学生怎么会错呢?
Of course, who am I to argue with a check-plus student?
嗯...
Mmm...
提醒你一下... 我会往右
Just warning you... I'm gonna go right.
别小题大作啊
Don't make a big deal out of it.
真的有必要化妆吗?
Is makeup really necessary?
别人看你的个人页面时
Well, when someone looks at your dating profile,
看的第一样东西就是你的照片
the first thing they see is your picture.
我想让你看起来风趣
I just want to make sure you look fun
充满活力 而不要
and full of life and not like a body
像一具刚从河里捞上来的尸体
they just pulled out of the river.
好吧 开始了...
All right, here we go, and...
微笑
smile.
好吧 呃... 这张备用
Okay, uh-uh, that one's in the bank.
这样如何?
How about this?
转过身 然后回眸看镜头
Turn away, and then turn back into it.
你想象一下
But when you do,
相机就是你想约的女孩
imagine the camera is the girl you want to meet.
没问题
You got it.
好吧 呃
Okay, uh,
我们再试一次
let's try it again.
但这次 假装你想约的女孩
Uh, but this time, pretend the girl you want to meet
不想伤害你
doesn't want to hurt you.
我觉得我做不出来
I don't think I can give you that.
拜托 再拍一次
Come on. One more time.
呃 有点 有点模糊了
Yeah, it's... it's a little blurry,
不过糊点更好
but I think that works in your favor.
想喝酒吗?
Do you want a beer?
好啊
Sure.
你的档案写完了吗?
Hey, have you finished writing your profile yet?
快了
Almost.
你是怎么用
Oh, what did you put
一个词描述自己的?
as the one-word description of yourself?
我写的是 无可非议
I put: unobjectionable.
但现在听起来
But now that I hear it out loud,
好像显得我有点自大了
it just seems like I'm being cocky.
最大优点那一栏你填的是什么?
What did you put for your best feature?
爸妈有钱
My parents' money.
那你是怎么填的?
Uh, what did you put for your best feature?
我写的: 不适用
I put: not applicable.
拜托 哥们 别对自己这么苛刻
Come on, dude, you're being too hard on yourself.
你有很多好东西的
You've got a lot of good stuff going on.
是吗? 比如?
Really? Like what?
说起来 你是... 你是出色的艺术家
Well, okay, you're a... you're a talented artist,
你有自己的生意
you own your own business.
但这些从没帮我找到过女人
Neither of those things have ever helped me meet a woman.
好吧 我们能暗示
Okay, well, can we imply
你命根子大吗?
that you're well-endowed?
我确实有一个出奇长的睾丸
I do have one oddly long testicle.
人生赢家啊!
Okay, now you're talking like a winner!
干嘛呢?
Whatcha doin'?
哦 我发现Amy最爱的傲慢与偏见
Oh, it turns out Amy's beloved Pride and Prejudice
是本完美无瑕的杰作
is a flawless masterpiece.
他太过骄傲
He's got too much pride,
她有很多偏见... 非常理所应当
she's got too much prejudice... it just works.
你打算在休闲版找点东西
So you're looking to ruin something for her
毁给她看?
in the funny pages?
Amy非常喜欢四格漫画马默杜克
Amy has a fondness for the comic strip Marmaduke.
嗯 然后呢...?
Mm-hmm. And...?
我觉得找到了 你想
And I think I've got it. Consider:
一家人有这么大一只狗
a family possesses a dog that is so large
而且不服管教 他除了捣乱什么都不会
and poorly disciplined, he causes nothing but problems.
他们干嘛还养他?!
Why do they keep him?!
或许它还小的时候很受宠爱
Maybe they fell in love with him as a puppy
他们也不知道他会变得这么大
and didn't know how big he was gonna be.
确实是
Of course.
你说 她怎么不喜欢Ziggy漫画呢?
You know, why couldn't she just like Ziggy?
为什么?
Yeah?
那剧情到处都是硬伤
That thing's riddled with plot holes.
- 抱歉 小伙伴  - 哦!
- Sorry, buddy.  - Ooh!
我记得她也是加菲猫的粉丝
I think she's a fan of Garfield as well.
哦 该死 现在我也是了
Oh, darn it, now so am I.
一会儿见
I'll see you later.
我要和Penny去看讨厌的足球赛
I gotta go watch a stupid football game with Penny.
慢着... 别急
Wait... hang on.
你和Amy相处过
You've spent time with Amy.
你能想到任何她喜欢的东西
Can you think of anything she's fond of
有一堆她没注意到的缺点吗?
that has a bunch of flaws she hasn't noticed?
(那不就是sheldon么)
我得走了
I gotta go.
准备好了吗?
You ready to go?
是的 这次你不用
Yep. Hey, and maybe this time
费心跟他们聊运动了
you don't try and talk sports with the guys.
那可是运动酒吧
Some sports bar.
就像他们从没听说过魁地奇似的(哈利波特中的魔法运动)
It's like they never even heard of Quidditch.
我们真的非去不可吗?
Do we really have to go?
拜托 每次我们要出去
Oh, come on. Every time we're about
和我朋友玩的时候 你都不想去
to hang out with my friends, you don't want to.
什么"太吵了"
It's like, "It's too loud,"
或者"厕所太脏了"
or "the bathroom's too dirty,"
还有"他们把鸡翅放我耳朵里了" 之类的...
or "they put a chicken wing in my ear..." I mean...
好吧 你... 你说得对
Well, you're... you're right.
去就去吧
Let's just go.
嘿 你到底怎么了?
Hey, what's going on with you?
没事 挺好的
Nothing, I'm fine.
好吧 慢着
All right, hang on.
还是因为你妈妈的书吗?
is this still about your mom's book?
不 不是所有事都是因为我妈
No. Not everything is about my mom.
因为如果你还为那事沮丧
'Cause if you're still upset about that,
我们可以不去的
we don't have to go.
不过这次完全是因为我妈
Except this is totally about my mom.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
我就不应该读那本书
I never should have read that book.
那我们出去吃个晚餐
You know what? You want to just get dinner
回来在电视上看比赛怎么样?
and watch the game here?
- 这主意还不错  - 好吧
- That sounds nice.  - Yeah. Okay.
或者我们可以叫点外卖
Or, you know, we could get take-out
然后看蓝光版未删减版
and watch the Blu-ray extended version
有导演解说音轨的"霍比特人"
of The Hobbit movie with commentary track.
谁让我妈这么伤我心呢
On account of how sad I am about my mom.
Leonard 去吃午饭啊?
Leonard, you ready for lunch?
马上!
One sec!
不好意思
Hey. Sorry.
嗨 Penny
Hi, Penny.
嗨
Hi.
好了 亲爱的
All right, sweetie.
在这好好干活
You hang in there today.
我尽量 但可能晚上我又会伤心了
I'll try, but I might be sad again tonight.
好吧
Okay.
哇呜!
Wow!
办公室嘿咻?!
Sex at work?!
别这么说
Leave it alone.
她是我女朋友
That's my girlfriend.
抱歉
Sorry.
我女朋友在办公室里和我嘿咻了!
Who just had sex with me at work!
你是怎么做到的?
Damn. How'd you swing that?
只要我一说我老妈对我多糟
Well, whenever I talk about how awful my mom was,
Penny就会想方设法想要安慰我
Penny will do anything to make me feel better.
- 真的啊?  - 我是说...
- Seriously?  - Look, I mean...
这么做不太光彩 但很管用啊
I'm not proud of it, but it does work.
她... 她竟然陪我看了
I... I got her to watch
全套六部"巨蟒剧团"的纪录片
a six-part documentary on Monty Python.
我都不想看了 但是我还是坚持
Even I was bored, I just wanted to see
想试试她能不能撑到最后
if she'd make it to the end.
你很自豪嘛
You sound kind of proud of it.
对 我真的很自豪
I am, I'm really proud.
嗯
Yeah.
嗨 Sheldon
Hello, Sheldon.
你还好吗?
Is everything okay?
嗯
Yes.
怎么了?
Why?
上一次你突然即兴
Well, the last time you made
跟我视频的时候
an unscheduled video-chat,
是你在一包直薯条里发现了一根弯的
there was a curly fry in your regular fries
你以为是有人给你下了药
and you thought someone might be trying to slip you a mickey.
四月13日...
April 13...
月黑风高的夜晚
a dark night, indeed.
那这次有什么事?
So what can I do for you?
我是想跟你说
I'm calling to invite you
明天晚上我们约会吧
to a spontaneous date night tomorrow evening.
真的?
Really?
嗯
Yes.
你都陪我看
You were kind enough
"夺宝奇兵"了
to watch Raiders of the Lost Ark with me.
所以我也想请你
So I'd like to return the favor
看一集你最喜欢的
by inviting you to watch an episode
儿童电视剧
of your favorite childhood television series,
"大草原上的小家"(作者维尔德)
Little House on the Prairie.
听起来不错
That sounds lovely.
你为什么摩拳擦掌的?
Why are you rubbing your hands together?
额...
Um...
我在擦护手霜
I'm putting on lotion.
你到底来不来?
Are you in or not?
当然去了
Of course I'm in.
太好了
Excellent.
那我们就明天见了
Then I shall see you tomorrow.
晚安 Fowler博士
Good night, Dr. Fowler.
晚安 Cooper博士
Good night, Dr. Cooper.
搞定了
Good night, indeed.
真是个土包子
What a rube.
我的纤纤玉手还用擦什么护手霜?
Why would I put on lotion when I have such soft hands?
你晚饭的时候都没说话
You were really quiet during dinner.
有什么事吗?
Is everything okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我只是想起我妈妈了
I guess I was just thinking about my mom,
还有我那悲惨的童年
and how sad my childhood was.
嗯 肯定挺难熬的
Yeah, I bet it sucked.
我要去洗个澡 你来洗碗吧
I'm gonna take a bath, you do the dishes.
我们俩一起洗怎么样
How about I take a bath with you
说不定有惊喜喔
and see what happens.
你听好了
Here's what's gonna happen:
我去洗澡
I'm gonna take a bath,
你去洗碗
and you're gonna do the dishes.
就这样?
That's it?
不安慰安慰我?
No compassion?
啊 可怜的Howie
Aw, poor Howie.
行了吧? 我去洗澡了
We good? I'm gonna take a bath.
Bernie啊...
Bernie...
天啊 你这是哪根筋不对?
God, what is going on with you?
我在倾诉我的苦痛呢
I'm sharing my pain.
我不买账 重来
And I'm not buying it. Try again.
我在一个迷失的文化中
I'm learning to be a man in a culture
艰难成长为一个男人...?
where it's increasingly difficult to know how...?
最后一次机会
Strike two.
我跟Leonard学得
I'm copying Leonard.
他每次跟Penny一装可怜
When he does this to Penny,
他们就滚床单 还看"巨蟒剧团"
they have sex and watch Monty Python.
- Howard!  - 我知道
- Howard!  - I know.
这很傻
It was dumb,
我不该这样
I shouldn't have done it.
我觉得自己很悲哀...
And it's making me feel sad...
太悲哀了
So sad.
你还是去洗澡吧 我去刷碗了
You know, why don't you take a bath? I'll do the dishes.
三 二 一...
Three, two, one...
搞定了
That's it.
我们的交友网站头像传好了
Our dating profiles are live on the Internet.
各位客官注意了:
Attention all shoppers:
本店正式开张营业!
my business is open for business!
放马过来吧 姑娘们
That's right, ladies.
可要知道
For all you know,
我浑身散发着自信幽默的气息喔
I'm confident and fun to be around.
不错啊 每次有人看
Oh, cool, it tells you
你的主页都会有提醒
when someone's reading your profile.
这个叫"Jenny309"
"Jenny309."
希望后边的数字不是她的体重
I hope that's not her weight.
如果是的话... 把她让给我
If it is, I'll... I'll take her.
好样的
Good one.
哦 也有人看我的了
Ooh, I got one, too.
姑娘们自己送上门来啊
The ladies are coming to us.
老天爷 要是我早几年开始玩这个
Oh, man, if I'd started this years ago,
到现在可能都已经离了两三次婚了
I'd be divorced two or three times by now.
什么... ? 又来一个
What... ? Another one.
你觉得不 怪... 怪怪的
You know, it... it's weird.
她们读你资料的时候 你...
When they're reading your profile, does it...
你觉不觉得没有安全感?
does it make you feel exposed?
就好像她们看到你全裸一样?
Like they see you naked?
她们又没尖叫着逃跑 所以 不觉得吧
Well, they're not running away screaming, so, no.
我爱死"大草原之家"了
I love Little House.
让我特别向往住在农场
It made me want to live on a farm so much
我还试着给我的猫挤过奶
I tried to milk my cat.
挤出的小小一碗臭糊糊
That tangy bowl of Cheerios
真不值得我被抓之后缝的那几针
was not worth the stitches.
你坐好 放轻松
Well, you sit back, relax
尽享回到童年的快乐之旅吧
and enjoy a beloved childhood memory.
看见那边那座小屋没?
You see that cabin there?
他们是私自占用印第安人的土地
I read they were illegally squatting on Indian land.
是啊
Yeah.
个人认为 我们对印第安原住民的
Personally, I think what we did
所作所为大错特错
to the Native Americans was wrong,
但这毕竟是你最爱的片子 不是我的
but this is your favorite show, not mine.
看看小萝拉·英格斯
Oh, look at little Laura Ingalls,
吃着那块花生黄油三明治
eating that peanut butter sandwich.
花生黄油?!
Peanut butter?!
嗬!
Huh!
这就怪了 因为花生黄油
That's strange, since peanut butter
直到上世纪初才问世
wasn't introduced until the early 1900s.
我要是事先知道这是部穿越剧
If I knew this show was about time travel,
我早就来看了
I would have watched it much sooner.
你在报复我
You're trying to get back at me
就为了我对"夺宝奇兵"的评价
for what I said about Raiders of the Lost Ark.
胡扯 怎么可能
That's silly.
简直跟贝克医生拥有电话这件事一样胡扯
Almost as silly as Dr. Baker having a telephone,
因为那个时期
since telephones only existed
电话只在大城市里才有
in large cities at that time.
这倒更像是部"大荒诞之家"
This is more like Little House on the Preposterous.
Sheldon 我们在谈恋爱
Sheldon, we're in a relationship.
你生气的时候 要跟我直说
When you get angry, just tell me.
没必要以牙还牙地报复
You don't need to seek revenge.
真的吗?
Are you sure?
每次我爸彻夜不归的时候
Every time my dad stayed out all night,
妈妈都会把仓鼠屎偷偷混进他的口嚼烟草里面
my mom would put hamster poop in his chewing tobacco.
不管 反正咱们之间不是这样的
Well, that's not how we're going to do it.
好吧
Fine.
我很生你的气
I'm mad at you.
不光是因为你毁了我的"夺宝奇兵"
Not only did you ruin Raiders for me,
你甚至毁了整个系列
you may have ruined the whole franchise.
除了第四部
Except for the fourth one,
那部自己就已经够糟的了
which was bad before you got your mitts on it.
我... 我当时不该那么说的
I... I shouldn't have said it.
我道歉
I'm sorry.
谢谢你
Thank you.
感觉好点了吗?
Do you feel better?
嗯
Yes.
但如果我告诉你这个之后我会更开心的
But not as good as I'm going to when I tell you
你亲爱的加菲猫根本没道理讨厌周一
that your precious Garfield has no reason to hate Mondays.
他是只猫 他又不用上班
He's a cat. He doesn't have a job.
嘿 我刚刚... 什么情况?
Hey, I was just... what is happening?
噢 就是犒劳你一下
Oh, just a little treat.
我知道最近一提到你妈
I know you've been feeling really bad
你就很难过
about your mom lately.
哦 我是很难过
Oh, oh, I have.
悲痛欲绝
So bad.
我想让你高兴高兴
And I wanted to make you feel better,
所以我为你准备了惊喜大礼包
so I planned something very special for you.
嗯哼
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
我已经惊喜得有反应了
I can already feel it working.
你好 Leonard
Hello, Leonard.
妈?!
Mom?!
我听说你最近为了在情感上控制你的女友
I understand you have been whining about my parenting
一直对我的抚养方式哭哭啼啼 抱怨个不停
in order to emotionally manipulate your girlfriend.
我... 呃...
I... uh...
Bernadette都告诉我了
Bernadette told me everything.
现在你左边右边哪边都甭想要了
Now you don't get the left or the right.
咱们来探讨一下
Let's discuss
你为何依然将我
why you continue to involve me
扯进你的性生活
in your sex life.
别了 求你了 妈妈
Oh, please, Mommy.
别了 妈妈
No, Mommy.
你六岁那年
When you were six years old,
走进房间 撞见我跟你爸一丝不挂
you walked in on me and your father naked.
我当时正用你新买的乒乓球拍
I was swatting his bottom
拍打他的屁股
with your brand new Ping Pong paddle.
原来我当时不是在做梦?
I didn't dream that?
你当时感觉如何?
How did that make you feel?
Penny 快回来!
Penny, come back!
我现在是真的难过了!
I'm sad for real now!
在过去两小时当中
In the last two hours,
有162个女人看了我们的资料
162 women have read our profiles.
多少人给咱们留言了?
How many of them have sent us messages?
- 加起来?  - 嗯
- Combined?  - Yes.
零个
Zero.
老兄 这... 这简直太残忍了
Dude, this is... this is brutal.
我以前从没受过这样的气
I don't think I've ever felt so rejected.
我可是救助过一只狗
And I had a rescue dog
那狗却跑走了的人啊
who ran back to the pound.
简直不可能更糟了
This is the worst.
要是咱们想被放倒
If we're gonna get shot down,
还不如跟以前一样
we might as well just go to a bar
直接去酒吧
and do it old school.
直视她们 看她还好意思拒绝
And make them look us in the eye.
就是 怎么都比这样强
Yeah, anything is better than this.
你好啊
Hello.
对你没兴趣
Not interested.
我错了 这样更糟
I was wrong. This is worse.
等等... 要不是因为印第安纳·琼斯
Wait, wait... if it wasn't for Indiana Jones,
约柜怎么会出现在仓库!
the ark would never have ended up at the warehouse!
没错儿!
That's true!
是他带上约柜
He collected and delivered the ark
交给当局保管的
to the proper authorities for filing.
大英雄啊!
Like a hero!
就是! 说得好!
Yeah! Yes! Right!
不过 理论上讲
Although, technically,
他本来应该把约柜
Indy was supposed to take the ark
带到一座博物馆给人研究的
to a museum to be studied.
可他连这种小事都没做到
He couldn't even get that done.
噢...
Aw...
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：影子打酱油 波特妹子 初见 捞盐不许再通宵
校对：UU在健身